you won't believe what happened to me today
what happened I love unexpected news
I got a job offer in New York
wow that's huge
are you going to take it
I'm thinking about it it's a big move
I can imagine how do you feel about leaving here
a bit sad but it's an amazing opportunity
definitely you have to grab chances like that
what about you any unexpected news recently
actually yes
I won a small lottery last week
no way that's incredible how much did you win
just $500 but it was a total surprise
that's still pretty cool
what will you do with it
I think I'll take a short vacation
a well deserved break where will you go
maybe a beach getaway I need some sun and sand
sounds like a perfect plan
it is but back to you
when do you decide about the job
I have to decide by next week
that's soon best of luck with your decision
thanks Sarah
I could use some good vibes